

Reverson Claudio Dias

Sn Infrastructure Engineer

♦ **Portugal, Braga** www.linkedin.com/in/reverson-dias-17b0a279

Profile

I have been working for more than 6 years in cloud computing environments. In all companies I'm ever involved in new challenges regarding new methodologies and tools. I'm passionate to automate process and build solutions. I've away been focused on implementing DevOps culture through the companies where I have worked.

Experience

Sn Infrastructure Engineer @ Bosch

01/2023 - present

- Work with AWS Kubernetes (EKS)
- Gitops approach with FluxCD
- Infrastructure delivery through Ansible

Sn Infrastructure Engineer @ Farfetch

05/2021 - 12/2022

- Work with Azure Kubernetes (AKS)
- Delivery the application through the ArgoCD
- Developing integration using golang

Sn Infrastructure Consultant @ ThoughtWorks

09/2020 - 03/2021

- Support and management AWS serverless environment (lambda)
- Created Terraform Modules

DevOps Engineer @ Geru

09/2019 - 09/2020

- Support and management Kubernetes platform (KOPS and EKS)
- $\hbox{- Improved CI/CD pipelines (Terraform+Ansible+CircleCi+Python)}\\$

Cloud Analyst (SRE) @ Itaú

09/2017 - 09/2019

- Supported an Openstack platform with more than 200 hosts
- Participated in the building Prometheus environment

Education

Specialization, Cloud Computing and Software-Defined Network

04/2019 - 12/2019

UNICAMP - Brazil

BA, Computer Science

2008 - 2011

Universidade São Francisco - Brazil

Details

10/01/1989

Braga – Portugal +351 914 147 958

reverino@gmail.com

Languages

English - Intermediate

Portuguese - Native

Tech Skill

CI/CD

Design Solutions

Infrastructure Archtecture

Linux

Kubernetes

Python

Ansible

Terraform

Prometheus

AWS

Docker

CicleCi

Shell

Git/Github

Prometheus/Thanos

Jenkins

Certificates

LPIC-1

LPIC-2

Kubernetes – CKA

Kubernetes - CKAD